natlawreview.com 2019-11-08

# The National Law Review Privacy Policy | The National Law Review

Welcome to the National Law Review (NLR). The NLR provides various services and products (collectively, the “Services”) to visitors using its Web site. Visitors include all users of the Web site (the “User[s]”), including users registering with the NLR (the “Registered User[s]”). The NLR may collect certain information from a User. The information may be voluntarily provided by the User or automatically recognized by the NLR’s server. The NLR cares about our Users’ information and is committed to the privacy and security of all its Users and Registered Users. This Privacy Policy explains the type of information that the NLR may collect and the treatment of such information.

This Privacy Policy only applies to NLR Services and not to the practices of companies that the NLR does not own or control, or to individuals that the NLR does not employ or manage, including operators of Web sites that Users may visit before, during, or after visiting the NLR Web site, and the owners or publishers of the documents, advertisements, or postings and other products (collectively, the “Publications”) Users download, review, or otherwise access through NLR Services. The NLR recommends that Users view the privacy policy statements of any companies, individuals, or organizations that may interface with the NLR in order to understand how they may collect, use, and share User information.

**A. Information We Collect**

The NLR Web site collects and stores two types of information: 1) information voluntarily provided by Users and Registered Users, and 2) information that is automatically recognized by the NLR’s Web server and stored whenever a User visits the NLR Web site. 

**1\. Voluntary Information** __

**a.** **Registration Data:** The NLR does not require registration to view content on our Web site. If the User wants to post documents, receive e-mail updates, advertise, post a blog answer or reply, or participate in other activities, the NLR may require certain limited information in order to process the User’s request. When the User registers for NLR Services and becomes a Registered User, the User may be asked to provide basic contact information such as name, company or organization name, address, phone number, professional title, and e-mail address (collectively, “Personal Information”). We use Personal Information to respond to the User’s inquiries, to post information provided by the User, and to send the User information as may be requested from time to time. 

**b.** **Order Data:** When a Registered User posts documents or places advertisements on the NLR Web site, the NLR collects various information including the Registered User’s address and billing information and, if required for payment processing, bank account information or credit card number and expiration date. Additionally, we request the author’s name, organization’s name (if any), contact information, and a brief biography of the author to be included with any document posted. Also, the NLR may store a Registered User’s photo(s) and/or firm logo, if such user chooses to include this material with any posted information. This information will be retained in the Registered User’s profile for the Registered User’s future use, if desired, when posting a specific article.

**c.** **Other Information:** We may collect additional information at other times, including but not limited to when the User provides feedback, changes content or e-mail preferences, responds to a survey, or communicates with NLR Customer Support. Additionally, the User may voluntarily provide an address and other information in order to be included in an NLR e-mail list. Furthermore, if the User elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site or for forwarding a document, we ask for the friend’s name and e-mail address. The NLR stores this information and may contact the friend to invite him or her to visit the NLR Web site. The friend may contact the NLR, if desired, to request the removal of this information from our database.

**2\. Automatically Recognized Information**

**a.** **Computer Configuration:** NLR automatically receives and logs information from the User’s browser, including IP address, computer name, operating system, browser type and version, CPU speed, and connection speed. 

**b.** **Referral, Click Stream, Site Interaction Data:** NLR may also record the URL that the User linked from to get to NLR’s Web site, the click stream through and from our Web site, and other generally accepted tracking information. 

**c.** **E-mail and Delivery Open Rates:** To help the NLR make our e-mail communications more useful and interesting, and to ensure that we are successfully delivering items to the User, we often receive a confirmation when a User receives and/or opens e-mail from the NLR.

**d.** **File Downloads and Publication Access:** When the User views and/or downloads Publications or other files from the NLR or forwards or prints Publications, we may record when each file transfer begins and ends, any errors that interrupt the transfer, and whether the User downloaded, forwarded, or accessed a given Publication.

**e.** **Updated Delivery and Address Information:** We may obtain updated contact information from third parties in order to correct our records and fulfill User orders or deliver communications to the User.

**f.** **Cookies:** Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that a Web site can store on a user’s computer hard drive. When a User visits the NLR and/or creates a Registered User account or downloads or purchases a product or service from us, we may set cookies on the User’s personal computer. We require that cookies be enabled in the User’s Web browser so that the NLR can identify the User as a repeat visitor or customer and maintain session information for Registered Users who are logged in; some services may not operate correctly unless the User enables his or her browser to accept cookies. The NLR uses cookies to track usage trends and patterns in order to better understand and improve areas of our Web site. The NLR may allow other companies that are providing content on its site to set and access their own cookies on the User’s computer. Other companies' use of cookies is subject to their respective privacy policies.

Such cookies do not collect any personal information such as name, age, phone number, e-mail address or mailing address. By using this website and/or clicking on any link on the website you confirm your consent to the NLR’s placing and usage of cookies in accordance with this privacy and cookies policy.  Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set your browser to reject cookies, more information on how to set your browser to reject cookies can be found [here](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

**B. Children**

The NLR Web site and Services are made available to the general public. However, NLR Services are not intended for children under the age of 13 and we require that Users be 13 years old or older. NLR markets to and collects information from Users and Registered Users as stated herein, but we do not do so intentionally or knowingly with respect to children under the age of 13. If the NLR determines that a User or Registered User has provided us with information and that such User is under the age of 13, NLR will delete this information as soon as possible once it is discovered. Anyone using the NLR Web site hereby represents that he or she is 13 years old or older. 

**C. How We Use the Information We Collect**

The NLR uses information it collects as follows: to display Publications a Registered User may post and in order to process other products (such as advertising); to verify access to secure content and Registered User’s account information; to determine whether the User's computer meets the minimum system requirements for use of NLR Services; to provide tailored content and instructions and targeted promotions; to service customer support requests; to add the User to any e-mail lists at User's request; to ask the User to participate in surveys about NLR products and services; and, to better understand, on an anonymous and aggregated basis, how NLR Services are being used, including Web traffic and reading patterns, so that we may continually improve NLR Services. 

**D. How We Share the Information We Collect**

We may share collected information as follows: 

**1.** **Publishers and Partners:** The NLR may provide its publishers and other merchants (advertisers) anonymous information collected automatically, such as information about the pages that Users are viewing, and may include IP addresses and other non-personally identifiable User data and browser types from Users of NLR Services. In such instances, Registered User’s Personal Information is governed by the privacy policies of such agents.

**2.** **Agents:** We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf such as sending e-mail, maintaining NLR Services, and processing credit card payments. Such agents will be provided limited access to Personal Information to the extent that it is needed to perform agent’s functions; agent shall not use such Personal Information for other purposes. In such instances, Registered User’s Personal Information is governed by the privacy policies of such agents.

**3.** **Protection of the NLR and Others:** The NLR, at its sole discretion and without prior permission from anyone, will disclose any information, including and not limited to account information and Personal Information, it deems necessary to comply with any law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of the NLR, our Users, or others.

**4.** **Business Transfers:** The NLR may transfer, sell, or assign information it collects, including any Personal Information, in connection with a business combination transaction, consolidation, liquidation, or sale or transfer of substantial assets of the NLR. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer or assignee of the NLR may continue to use Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**E. Security**

This Web site takes reasonable security precautions to protect User and Registered User information. Order Data information will be stored in a database located behind firewalls and accessible only to authorized personnel. The NLR does not encrypt normal Web sessions, but any transmission of credit card or other order data to our servers uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information provided by Users. Password and credit card information is then stored in the NLR database in an encrypted, nonhuman-readable form. 

Please note that no method of transmitting or storing data is completely secure, and therefore we cannot guarantee the security of User and Registered User information. Unauthorized entry into or unauthorized use of NLR Services, hardware, or software; transmissions failure; or other factors may compromise the security of User information. If you have reason to believe your interaction with NLR Service is no longer secure, you must notify the NLR immediately. Likewise, if the NLR suspects that the security of User information in our possession and control may have been compromised, the NLR will seek to notify the User of the situation as promptly as circumstances allow. If you have any questions about the security of the NLR Web site, or need to contact us if you suspect a security breach, please e-mail us at [info@natlawreview.com](mailto:info@natlawreview.com). 

**F. Correcting/Updating Personal Information**

If a Registered User’s Personal Information changes, or if a Registered User no longer desires our services, such Registered User is required to notify the NLR. This can usually be done at the “User Account” page or by sending an e-mail to [info@natlawreview.com](http://info@natlawreview.com/). 

**G. Notification of Changes**

The NLR reserves the right to amend and modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on the NLR Web site. When visiting the NLR Web site, Users should check the [Privacy Policy](https://www.natlawreview.com/national-law-review-s-privacy-policy) at [www.natlawreview.com/national-law-review-s-privacy-policy](https://www.natlawreview.com/national-law-review-s-privacy-policy) for any changes. This Privacy Policy, and any modifications to it, are incorporated and made a part of the Terms of Use posted on the NLR Web site, and Users and Registered Users are bound to the terms of the Privacy Policy as modified from time to time. If Users and Registered Users do not agree to the Privacy Policy as modified, the Users and Registered Users shall immediately stop using NLR Services, and Registered Users shall cancel their accounts. The NLR reserves the right to prevent any User or Registered User from accessing its Services, if NLR, in its sole discretion, decides that such User or Registered User is in violation of the Privacy Policy and as it may be modified. 

**H. How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or our use of your information, please contact us via e-mail at [info@natlawreview.com](mailto:info@natlawreview.com) or write to us at The National Law Review, National Law Forum, LLC, 4700 Gilbert, Suite 47 (#230), Western Springs, IL 60558. 

_This Policy is effective as of May 22, 2009.   _
